♪The neon lights before the French windows shining at 3 AM♪
♪ أضواء النيون أمام النوافذ الفرنسية تلمع الساعة 3 فجرا ♪
♪The pile of old photos is getting dusty♪
كومة الصور القديمة تتغبر
♪It's the season of reunion♪
♪ إنه موسم لم الشمل ♪
♪The gentle breeze is brushing my cheek♪
النسيم اللطيف يفرش خدي
♪You failed to see me in the crowd♪
♪ لقد فشلت في رؤيتي وسط الحشد ♪
♪The neon lights are bright, but I can't find you in the crowd♪
♪ أضواء النيون ساطعة لكن لا أجدك وسط الزحام
♪I can sense that you're avoiding me♪
♪ أستطيع أن أشعر أنك تتجنبني
♪On the empty street♪
في الشارع الخالي ♪
♪Where the neon lights are shining alone♪
حيث تسطع أضواء النيون وحدها
♪Just like our reunion♪
♪ تمامًا مثل لم شملنا ♪
♪The neon lights are blinking, and I failed to get closer to you♪
♪ أضواء النيون تومض ، وفشلت في الاقتراب منك
♪Some have already forgotten♪
♪ لقد نسي البعض بالفعل
♪The fragments of memories♪
شظايا الذكريات ♪
♪Will fade one day like neon lights♪
♪ سوف تتلاشى يومًا ما مثل أضواء النيون
♪By then, can we get the spark back?♪
♪ بحلول ذلك الوقت ، هل يمكننا استعادة الشرارة؟
[To Be A Brave One]
[أن تكون شجاعًا]
[Episode 30]
[الحلقة 30]
Nice one!
هذا لطيف!
I'm so happy!
انا سعيد للغاية!
That was nerve-racking.
كان ذلك مرهقا للأعصاب.
An Yu.
آن يو.
Good job.
أحسنت.
It's time
حان الوقت
for my life to move on to the next stage.
لحياتي للانتقال إلى المرحلة التالية.
You were great today.
لقد كنت رائعًا اليوم.
Coming.
آت.
Morning.
صباح.
Why are you up so early?
لماذا انت مستيقظ باكرا؟
It's not that early.
لم يكن ذلك في وقت مبكر.
Come on, let's head out.
تعال ، دعنا نخرج.
Aren't you tired?
ألست متعب؟
You just competed yesterday.
لقد تنافست بالأمس للتو.
No, I'm not.
لا أنا لست كذلك.
Look.
نظرة.
You've got a wound on your face.
لديك جرح في وجهك.
It's just a little scratch.
إنه مجرد خدش صغير.
It's nothing.
إنه لاشيء.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Get changed and let's go have fun.
تغير ودعنا نمرح.
[Yimi Capital Mortgage Contract]
[عقد الرهن العقاري لشركة Yimi Capital]
[Real Estate Mortgage Agreement]
[اتفاقية الرهن العقاري]
I'm in a really good mood today.
أنا في مزاج جيد حقًا اليوم.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
It's not solely because I won the competition.
ليس فقط لأنني فزت بالمسابقة.
Why do you know everything?
لماذا تعرف كل شيء؟
I know you made a very difficult decision.
أعلم أنك اتخذت قرارًا صعبًا للغاية.
When you won the competition.
عندما فزت بالمسابقة.
You even know that?
أنت تعرف ذلك حتى؟
Whenever you're in a bad mood,
عندما تكون في مزاج سيء ،
you'll go boxing.
ستذهب للملاكمة.
This time, you even joined a competition.
هذه المرة ، حتى انضممت إلى مسابقة.
It must have meant you were in a huge dilemma
لابد أن هذا يعني أنك كنت في معضلة كبيرة
and it weighed heavily on you.
وقد أثر عليك بشدة.
I later learned
علمت فيما بعد
that Lin Zhanhong wanted to use Zhuoyue's shares
أن Lin Zhanhong أراد استخدام أسهم Zhuoyue
in exchange for He Shuo's copyright.
في مقابل حقوق النشر الخاصة بـ He Shuo.
I suspected he had another motive.
كنت أظن أن لديه دافعًا آخر.
So I asked him.
لذلك سألته.
And he admitted
واعترف
that he wanted you to cooperate with him.
أنه يريدك أن تتعاون معه.
I understood then
فهمت بعد ذلك
that you were facing
التي كنت تواجهها
a very important decision.
قرار مهم جدا.
Whether or not to seek revenge.
سواء كنت تسعى للانتقام أم لا.
So you've always known.
لذلك كنت دائما على علم.
And you've been supporting me.
وأنت كنت تدعمني.
An Yu.
آن يو.
I really admire you.
أنا معجب بك حقًا.
I always tell you
انا اقول لك دائما
and urge you
وحثك
to let it go.
لتتركها تذهب.
Let it go.
دعها تذهب.
♪Both blurry and clear♪
♪ كلاهما ضبابي وواضح ♪
But I really can't imagine
لكنني حقًا لا أستطيع أن أتخيل
that if all of this had happened to me,
أنه إذا حدث لي كل هذا ،
♪The wind blows your dress up♪
♪ الرياح تهب فستانك ♪
would I be able to be as brave as you
هل سأكون قادرًا على أن أكون شجاعًا مثلك
♪You're like a poem♪
♪ أنت مثل القصيدة ♪
and be as firm as you?
وتكون حازما مثلك؟
And at last,
وايضا الاخير،
♪That captivates me♪
هذا يأسرني ♪
overcome it like you.
تغلب عليه مثلك.
♪I listen to the wind and you quietly♪
♪ أستمع إلى الريح وأنت بهدوء ♪
♪The eraser that has removed our innocence♪
الممحاة التي أزالت براءتنا
You must be exhausted.
يجب أن تكون مرهقًا.
♪I ask myself♪
♪ أسأل نفسي ♪
♪You're the reason I persevere♪
♪ أنت سبب مثابري ♪
You did well.
لقد أبليت حسنا.
♪You broke through the darkness♪
اخترقت الظلام ♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪ ونمت أجنحة جديدة
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪ يقودني إلى ضربة بضربة لخلق دراما ♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
لا يمكن استخلاصه ♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
أحدق فيك ، كلهم ​​مهووسون ، ولا يمكنني التوقف
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪ فتحت الدرج بغير قصد
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
التي احتفظت فيها بالرسومات التي رسمتها معك ♪
During this time,
خلال هذه المده،
the biggest impression I got
أكبر انطباع لدي
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪ ولا أعرف أين أنت الآن ♪
is how hard it was to live with hatred.
هو مدى صعوبة التعايش مع الكراهية.
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪ صداقتنا المفقودة منذ زمن طويل ♪
♪Our future together♪
مستقبلنا معًا
Is the amusement park boring?
هل مدينة الملاهي مملة؟
Is the ice cream not good?
هل الآيس كريم ليس جيدًا؟
Is the sunlight not warm?
هل ضوء الشمس غير دافئ؟
Is the husky ugly?
هل الهاسكي قبيح؟
Why should we waste our lives
لماذا نضيع حياتنا
on those people?
على هؤلاء الناس؟
♪You draw all my attention♪
أنت تلفت انتباهي كله ♪
Right.
الصحيح.
You should waste your life
يجب أن تضيع حياتك
on me.
علي.
♪I listen to the wind and you quietly♪
♪ أستمع إلى الريح وأنت بهدوء ♪
Alright then.
حسنا اذا.
Should we ride on the roller coaster or the pirate ship?
هل يجب أن نركب السفينة الدوارة أم سفينة القراصنة؟
What?
ماذا؟
Are you trying to get back at me?
هل تحاول العودة إلي؟
So deliberate.
متعمد جدا.
Yes.
نعم.
It's deliberate.
إنه متعمد.
This way, you'll get the chance
بهذه الطريقة ، ستحصل على الفرصة
to hug me and hold onto me.
لتحتضنني وتمسك بي.
Well,
نحن سوف،
I'm not going to let go anyway.
لن أتركه على أي حال.
♪And grew new wings♪
♪ ونمت أجنحة جديدة
Hug me.
احضنّي.
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪ يقودني إلى ضربة بضربة لخلق دراما ♪
I'm older, so you'll do as I say.
أنا أكبر سنًا ، لذا ستفعل ما أقول.
♪That cannot be drawn♪
لا يمكن استخلاصه ♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
أحدق فيك ، كلهم ​​مهووسون ، ولا يمكنني التوقف
Thank goodness I have you.
شكرا لله لدي لك.
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪ فتحت الدرج بغير قصد
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
التي احتفظت فيها بالرسومات التي رسمتها معك ♪
I'll always be here.
سأكون دائما هنا.
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪ لم نلتقي منذ بعض الوقت ♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪ ولا أعرف أين أنت الآن ♪
I love you.
أحبك.
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪ صداقتنا المفقودة منذ زمن طويل ♪
♪Our future together♪
مستقبلنا معًا
I need to answer the call.
أنا بحاجة للرد على المكالمة.
No, you won't.
لا ، لن تفعل.
You're having fun today.
أنت تستمتع اليوم.
No answering phone calls.
لا يوجد رد على المكالمات الهاتفية.
I still have to answer calls when I'm having fun.
ما زلت مضطرًا للرد على المكالمات عندما أستمتع.
[Mi Lu]
[مي لو]
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I'd like to meet with you.
أود مقابلتك.
Can I?
هل استطيع؟
You wanted to see me?
اردت رؤيتي؟
Please take a seat.
رجاءا اجلس.
I...
أنا...
I only found out recently
اكتشفت مؤخرا فقط
that you and Zhou Yuan
أن أنت و Zhou Yuan
were childhood sweethearts who grew up together.
كانوا أحباء الطفولة الذين نشأوا معًا.
Perhaps in this complicated relationship,
ربما في هذه العلاقة المعقدة ،
I was the one
لقد كنت الوحيد
who shouldn't be in the picture.
من لا يجب أن يكون في الصورة.
Growing up,
يشبون،
a lot of things happened between us.
حدثت الكثير من الأشياء بيننا.
I always believed
كنت دائما أؤمن
that he didn't love you.
أنه لم يحبك.
Even though you have a child,
على الرغم من أن لديك طفلًا ،
that must have been an accident.
يجب أن يكون حادث.
He sent you photos of Yiyi
أرسل لك صور Yiyi
and kept asking you to meet up.
وظل يطلب منك أن تقابل.
I tried to convince myself
حاولت إقناع نفسي
that it was out of guilt.
أنه كان بدافع الشعور بالذنب.
Not love.
ليس حب.
Until I saw this photo
حتى رأيت هذه الصورة
at home just now.
في المنزل الآن.
To me, all of that
بالنسبة لي ، كل ذلك
feels like something from a past life.
يبدو وكأنه شيء من الحياة الماضية.
Now, I'm like an outsider looking in.
الآن ، أنا مثل شخص خارجي ينظر إلى الداخل.
You don't have to be concerned at all.
لا داعي للقلق على الإطلاق.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
It's presumptuous of me to ask to meet you today.
من الفخامة أن أطلب مقابلتك اليوم.
But I'm out of options.
لكنني خارج الخيارات.
Just now at home,
الآن في المنزل ،
I received his house mortgage notice
تلقيت إشعار الرهن العقاري لمنزله
as well as all the contracts pertaining to Yimi.
وكذلك جميع العقود المتعلقة بـ Yimi.
He's lost all semblance of sanity.
لقد فقد كل مظاهر العقل.
At that moment, I felt
شعرت في تلك اللحظة
like he was standing alone at the edge of the cliff.
كما لو كان يقف بمفرده على حافة الجرف.
If he acquired your shares too,
إذا حصل على أسهمك أيضًا ،
he could very fall into the abyss.
يمكن أن يسقط في الهاوية.
So please, An Yu.
لذا أرجوك يا آن يو.
Don't sell him your shares.
لا تبيعه أسهمك.
Think of it as saving him.
فكر في الأمر على أنه إنقاذ له.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I won't sell them to him.
لن أبيعهم له.
Actually, before coming here,
في الواقع ، قبل المجيء إلى هنا ،
I've already made a decision.
لقد اتخذت قرارًا بالفعل.
Give this equity transfer contract
امنح عقد تحويل حقوق الملكية هذا
back to him
العودة إليه
and tell him
وأخبره
that it's all over.
أن كل شيء قد انتهى.
If there's nothing else,
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر ،
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
An Yu.
آن يو.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
If you wish to see Yiyi,
إذا كنت ترغب في رؤية Yiyi ،
you can visit him every week.
يمكنك زيارته كل أسبوع.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I hope you can talk some sense into him.
أتمنى أن تتحدث معه ببعض المنطق.
You're back.
لقد عدت.
Why do you have this?
لماذا لديك هذا؟
An Yu won't sell her shares to you.
لن تبيع An Yu أسهمها لك.
I've told her everything.
لقد قلت لها كل شيء.
What on earth?
ماذا على الارض؟
Why did you do that?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
Because I want to protect this family.
لأنني أريد حماية هذه العائلة.
With Yimi's current assets,
مع الأصول الحالية ييمي ،
there's no way it can compete with Zhuoyue.
لا توجد طريقة يمكنها من خلالها منافسة Zhuoyue.
You put a mortgage on all the assets.
يمكنك وضع رهن عقاري على جميع الأصول.
Not just Yimi, right?
ليس فقط Yimi ، أليس كذلك؟
You even mortgaged the house!
حتى أنك رهن المنزل!
Once I've attained my goal
بمجرد أن حققت هدفي
and acquired Zhuoyue,
واكتسبت Zhuoyue ،
I can get all those things back.
يمكنني استعادة كل هذه الأشياء.
Don't you know
لا تعرف
you just
انت فقط
ruined everything I've done so far?
دمر كل ما فعلته حتى الآن؟
Zhou Yuan.
تشو يوان.
It hasn't been easy for us to get here.
لم يكن من السهل علينا الوصول إلى هنا.
Please stop.
توقف أرجوك.
-I'm begging you. -How can I stop?
-أتوسل إليك.  - كيف يمكنني التوقف؟
It's not too late to stop.
لم يفت الأوان للتوقف.
If you won't stop now,
إذا لم تتوقف الآن ،
it will really be too late to go back.
سيكون الوقت قد فات للعودة.
There's no going back!
ليس هناك عودة!
I've already come this far.
لقد وصلت بالفعل إلى هذا الحد.
Do you think I can still back out?
هل تعتقد أنه لا يزال بإمكاني التراجع؟
What do you mean by you can't back out?
ماذا تقصد لا يمكنك التراجع؟
Tell me the truth.
أخبرني الحقيقة.
Do you think An Wenbin did those things
هل تعتقد أن أن وينبين فعل هذه الأشياء
of his own volition?
بمحض إرادته؟
If not for me,
إذا لم يكن الأمر كذلك بالنسبة لي ،
he wouldn't have done so.
لم يكن ليفعل ذلك.
So you've been lying to me all this while.
لذلك كنت تكذب علي كل هذا الوقت.
An Wenbin going to jail
يذهب وينبين إلى السجن
and everything that happened after.
وكل ما حدث بعد ذلك.
You set all of it up, didn't you?
قمت بإعداد كل ذلك ، أليس كذلك؟
He deserved what he got!
إنه يستحق ما تلقاه!
All this while,
كل هذه الفترة،
I thought I was the one who knew you best.
اعتقدت أنني كنت أفضل من أعرفك.
Now you just seem like a stranger to me.
الآن تبدو وكأنك غريب بالنسبة لي.
Don't show any mercy.
لا تظهر أي رحمة.
A debt must be paid. It's only right.
يجب دفع الدين.  هذا صحيح فقط.
Who are you people?
من انتم ايها الناس؟
We came to demand payment.
جئنا للمطالبة بالدفع.
Mr. An.
السيد.
The money he owes me
المال الذي يدين لي به
is more than all of you combined.
أكثر من أنتم جميعًا مجتمعين.
You guys stay out of it!
أنتم يا رفاق ابقوا خارجها!
Scram!
انصرف!
You heard us. Scram!
سمعتنا.  انصرف!
You two, guard the entrance.
أنتما الاثنان ، حراسة المدخل.
Hu.
هو.
You two guard the staircase.
أنتما الاثنان تحرسان الدرج.
Stop anyone
أوقف أي شخص
asking for payment.
يسأل عن الدفع.
Got it, Mr. An.
حسنًا ، سيد "آن".
[A debt must be paid. It's only right. Pay up, Xiao Feng!]
[يجب دفع الدين.  هذا صحيح فقط.  ادفع يا شياو فنغ!]
I met with Mi Lu.
التقيت مع مي لو.
I gave her back the contract.
لقد أعدت لها العقد.
You have to sell those shares to me.
عليك أن تبيع تلك الأسهم لي.
You have to sign it.
يجب عليك التوقيع عليه.
I'm not selling you anything.
أنا لا أبيع لك أي شيء.
I know what Mi Lu said to you.
أعرف ما قاله لك مي لو.
Don't listen to her.
لا تستمع إليها.
With my capabilities,
بإمكانياتي ،
I can buy all the shares, no problem.
يمكنني شراء جميع الأسهم ، لا مشكلة.
You don't have to worry about me.
لا داعي للقلق علي.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I made the decision before Mi Lu came to me.
لقد اتخذت القرار قبل أن يأتي مي لو لي.
At first,
في البدايه،
I did want to get revenge.
كنت أرغب في الانتقام.
So I went along with your plan.
لذلك ذهبت مع خطتك.
But later I realized.
لكنني أدركت لاحقًا.
Even if you lost everything,
حتى لو فقدت كل شيء ،
what joy would that give me?
ما هي الفرحة التي ستمنحني؟
So I won't sell
لذلك لن أبيع
the shares to you.
الأسهم لك.
So, why wouldn't you continue playing along?
لذا ، لماذا لا تستمر في اللعب؟
You should've continued with the act a little longer.
كان يجب أن تستمر في الفعل لفترة أطول قليلاً.
That way, you would know what I've been through over the years.
بهذه الطريقة ، ستعرف ما مررت به على مر السنين.
Do you think what you know is the whole truth?
هل تعتقد أن ما تعرفه هو الحقيقة الكاملة؟
You have no idea
ليس لديك فكرة
why I'm doing all this.
لماذا أفعل كل هذا.
So why?
اذا لماذا؟
When I was 13,
عندما كان عمري 13 عامًا ،
my dad died in an accident.
توفي والدي في حادث.
But it wasn't an accident.
لكنها لم تكن مصادفة.
He jumped to his death because of dunning.
لقد قفز حتى وفاته بسبب الدعارة.
On that day,
في ذلك اليوم،
I saw my father fall to his death
رأيت والدي يسقط حتى وفاته
with my own eyes.
بأم عيني.
And the person who pushed him to death
والشخص الذي دفعه حتى الموت
was your father, An Wenbin.
كان والدك ، أن وينبين.
And Zhou Yuan isn't my real name.
و Zhou Yuan ليس اسمي الحقيقي.
My name is Xiao Yong.
اسمي شياو يونغ.
I'm Xiao Feng's son.
أنا ابن شياو فنغ.
So right from the start, our relationship,
لذا منذ البداية ، علاقتنا ،
even our first meeting,
حتى أول اجتماع لنا ،
was part of your plan.
كان جزءًا من خطتك.
Those things I did to your dad,
تلك الأشياء التي فعلتها لوالدك ،
I never once regret it.
أنا لا أندم مرة واحدة على ذلك.
But that's in the past.
لكن هذا في الماضي.
You're the exception.
أنت الاستثناء.
I really feel bad.
أشعر حقا بالسوء.
How could you not feel regretful
كيف لا تشعر بالندم
for the things you did to my dad?
على الأشياء التي فعلتها لأبي؟
That's what he owed my dad.
هذا ما كان يدين به لأبي.
Why would I regret it?
لماذا أندم على ذلك؟
No way.
مستحيل.
My dad wasn't that kind of person.
لم يكن والدي من هذا النوع من الأشخاص.
He wouldn't do such a thing.
لن يفعل مثل هذا الشيء.
I saw it with my own eyes.
رأيت ذلك بعيني.
How could it be wrong?
كيف يمكن أن يكون خطأ؟
And Lin Zhanhong.
ولين زان هونغ.
If he hadn't refused
إذا لم يرفض
to save my dad,
لإنقاذ والدي ،
my dad wouldn't have died.
لم يمت والدي.
So I'm going through with this no matter what.
لذلك أنا أمر بهذا بغض النظر عن أي شيء.
You must sell me the shares.
يجب أن تبيع لي الأسهم.
Zhou Yuan.
تشو يوان.
After everything that has happened,
بعد كل ما حدث ،
you are now standing at the edge of the cliff.
أنت الآن تقف على حافة الهاوية.
For the sake of Yiyi
من أجل Yiyi
and Mi Lu,
ومي لو ،
won't you stop this insanity?
ألا توقف هذا الجنون؟
So,
لذا،
you're set
أنت على استعداد
on not selling me the shares,
على عدم بيع الأسهم لي ،
right?
الصحيح؟
I'm not selling them to you.
أنا لا أبيعها لك.
Okay.
تمام.
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
Hello, Mr. He.
مرحبا سيد.
I've decided.
لقد قررت.
I'll sign the contract.
سأوقع العقد.
Come in.
ادخل.
Ms. Fang.
السيدة فانغ.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Anything you need?
أي شيء تريد؟
It's nothing.
إنه لاشيء.
You've been busy the whole day.
كنت مشغولا طوال اليوم.
You probably haven't had dinner.
ربما لم تتناولي العشاء.
I happen to have some supper.
تصادف أن تناولت بعض العشاء.
Would you like to eat?
هل ترغب في أكل؟
No, thanks.
لا شكرا.
I'm in a rush.
أنا في عجلة من أمري.
It's late.
الوقت متاخر.
Are you still going to the hospital?
هل مازلت ذاهبة إلى المستشفى؟
Does that concern you?
هل هذا يهمك؟
No.
رقم.
I don't mean anything else, Ms. Fang.
لا أقصد أي شيء آخر ، السيدة فانغ.
I'm just saying
أنا فقط أقول
that if you're tired, you should go home and rest.
أنه إذا كنت متعبًا ، فعليك العودة إلى المنزل والراحة.
I can go on your behalf.
يمكنني الذهاب نيابة عنك.
This is my personal matter.
هذه هي شأني الشخصي.
It has nothing to do with you.
لا علاقة لك به.
I know, I get it.
أنا أعلم ، فهمت.
It has nothing to do with me.
لا يمتلك شيئا ليفعله معي.
I see how tired you are.
أرى كم أنت متعب.
I think you should take more rest.
أعتقد أنك يجب أن تأخذ المزيد من الراحة.
I can go to the hospital and look after Fangfang.
يمكنني الذهاب إلى المستشفى والاعتناء بـ Fangfang.
I hear you.
اسمعك.
Thanks for the offer.
شكرا على العرض.
But in the future,
لكن في المستقبل
please don't meddle in other people's business.
من فضلك لا تتدخل في أعمال الآخرين.
Yu.
يو.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
I'd like to ask you about
أود أن أسألك عن
some things from the past.
بعض الأشياء من الماضي.
Things from the past?
أشياء من الماضي؟
Regarding Mr. Xiao Feng's suicide
بخصوص انتحار السيد شياو فنغ
20 years ago.
قبل 20 عاما.
How are you and my father
كيف حالك ووالدي
related
ذات صلة
to the incident?
للحادث؟
Zhou Yuan told you?
قال لك تشو يوان؟
Yes.
نعم.
He told me everything.
قال لي كل شيء.
What about you?
وماذا عنك؟
Did you come clean with him too?
هل أتيت نظيفة معه أيضًا؟
Regarding the shares,
فيما يتعلق بالأسهم ،
I've decided to stop deceiving him.
لقد قررت التوقف عن خداعه.
Yu.
يو.
How could you be so foolish?
كيف يمكن أن تكون بهذا الغباء؟
Don't you want to avenge your father?
ألا تريد الانتقام من والدك؟
What happened at the time is old history.
ما حدث في ذلك الوقت هو تاريخ قديم.
The people involved are gone.
ذهب الأشخاص المتورطون.
Who can provide the truth?
من يستطيع تقديم الحقيقة؟
But four years ago,
لكن قبل أربع سنوات ،
Zhou Yuan caused Xingchen Financial
تسبب Zhou Yuan في Xingchen Financial
to go bankrupt.
ان تفلس.
Because of him, you and your father were sent to prison.
بسببه ، تم إرسالك أنت ووالدك إلى السجن.
That's an undeniable fact.
هذه حقيقة لا يمكن إنكارها.
Didn't we agree?
ألم نتفق؟
That we'd take back
أننا سوف نستعيدها
what your father had lost?
ماذا فقد والدك؟
To accomplish our plan,
لإنجاز خطتنا ،
and to give
والعطاء
the Smart Desk project
مشروع Smart Desk
you value highly a push,
أنت تقدّر دفعة كبيرة ،
I've exchanged much of Zhuoyue's assets
لقد قمت بتبادل الكثير من أصول Zhuoyue
with He Shuo.
مع هو Shuo.
We're already at this step.
نحن بالفعل في هذه الخطوة.
How could you just give up like this?
كيف يمكنك أن تتخلى عن مثل هذا؟
Did you really do all that
هل فعلت كل ذلك حقًا
just to help me?
فقط لمساعدتي؟
Yu.
يو.
You know what?
أتعلم؟
Twenty years ago,
قبل عشرين عاما ،
when this building was still unfinished,
عندما كان هذا المبنى لا يزال غير مكتمل ،
your father, Mr. Xiao, and I
والدك السيد شياو وأنا
had stood at this spot too.
وقفت في هذا المكان أيضًا.
Back then, the three of us
في ذلك الوقت ، نحن الثلاثة
didn't even have 10,000 in our pockets.
لم يكن لدينا حتى 10000 في جيوبنا.
For that entire night, we shouted
طوال تلك الليلة ، صرخنا
how we wished to become China's biggest financial corporation.
كيف تمنينا أن نصبح أكبر شركة مالية في الصين.
When you're older,
عندما تكبر ،
it's easy to get sentimental.
من السهل أن تصبح عاطفيًا.
Every time I see you,
كل مرة أراك فيها،
I am always
انا دائما
reminded of your father.
تذكر والدك.
I remember those days when we worked hard together.
أتذكر تلك الأيام التي عملنا فيها بجد معًا.
Back then, together with my buddies...
في ذلك الوقت ، مع رفاقي ...
Then can you tell me
ثم هل يمكن أن تخبرني
what really happened back then?
ما الذي حدث بالفعل في ذلك الوقت؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Are you sure?
هل أنت واثق؟
Okay.
تمام.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Got it.
فهمتك.
An Yu.
آن يو.
The things that happened 20 years ago,
الأشياء التي حدثت قبل 20 عامًا ،
let's not worry about that.
دعونا لا نقلق بشأن ذلك.
Let's put it behind us.
دعونا نضعها وراءنا.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
Madam.
سيدتي.
You're here.
أنت هنا.
Is Fangfang all right?
هل Fangfang بخير؟
He's fine.
انه على ما يرام.
I fell asleep last night
نمت الليله الماضيه
and couldn't come.
ولا يمكن أن تأتي.
You must be tired,
يجب أن تكون متعبًا ،
handling everything yourself.
التعامل مع كل شيء بنفسك.
It's taking a toll on you.
إنه يضر بك.
Thankfully, you have help now.
لحسن الحظ ، لديك مساعدة الآن.
It will lighten your load.
سوف يخفف الحمل الخاص بك.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Su.
هم انهم.
He's been here since last night.
لقد كان هنا منذ الليلة الماضية.
I think he hasn't left.
أعتقد أنه لم يغادر.
Go on.
تابع.
Ms. Fang.
السيدة فانغ.
Didn't I tell you not to come?
ألم أقل لك لا تأتي؟
Ms. Fang, please don't get me wrong.
السيدة فانغ ، من فضلك لا تفهموني خطأ.
I...
أنا...
My neighbor upstairs got a new dog.
حصل جاري في الطابق العلوي على كلب جديد.
I think it's a husky.
أعتقد أنه من أجش.
It's always barking.
إنه ينبح دائمًا.
I couldn't sleep at all.
لم أستطع النوم على الإطلاق.
I just paid the rent.
لقد دفعت الإيجار للتو.
It will be my loss if I moved out.
ستكون خسارتي إذا خرجت.
I'm timid.
أنا خجول.
I don't feel comfortable troubling others.
لا أشعر بالراحة في إزعاج الآخرين.
So I thought I could sleep here.
لذلك اعتقدت أنني أستطيع النوم هنا.
It's quiet
إنه هادئ
and without disruption.
وبدون انقطاع.
At the same time,
في نفس الوقت،
I could accompany Chen Fang.
يمكنني مرافقة تشين فانغ.
Ms. Fang.
السيدة فانغ.
Think of it as helping me out.
فكر في الأمر على أنه يساعدني.
Next time, you take Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays.
في المرة القادمة ، تأخذ أيام الاثنين والأربعاء والجمعة.
I'll take Tuesdays, Thursdays, and Saturdays.
سآخذ أيام الثلاثاء والخميس والسبت.
I'll be able to sleep three nights a week.
سأتمكن من النوم ثلاث ليال في الأسبوع.
You can have more rest too.
يمكنك الحصول على المزيد من الراحة أيضًا.
It's decided then.
قضى الامر.
I'll go get breakfast.
سأذهب لتناول الإفطار.
Ms. Fang.
السيدة فانغ.
These are the project reports you asked for.
هذه هي تقارير المشروع التي طلبتها.
Are these all?
هل هذه كلها؟
What about those that weren't voted in?
ماذا عن أولئك الذين لم يتم التصويت لهم؟
The fire-fighting drones,
طائرات الإطفاء بدون طيار ،
Pony Online Education,
تعليم المهر عبر الإنترنت ،
and the peptide biopharmaceuticals.
والمستحضرات الصيدلانية الحيوية الببتيدية.
You want those too?
تريد هؤلاء أيضا؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Those are still in the preliminary assessment
هؤلاء لا يزالون في التقييم الأولي
and are held at the Risk Management Team.
ويتم احتجازهم في فريق إدارة المخاطر.
Yes.
نعم.
Go get them
اذهب واحضرهم
and add them to the report.
وإضافتها إلى التقرير.
Particularly on the expected revenue segment.
لا سيما على قطاع الإيرادات المتوقعة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Okay.
تمام.
Look at this part.
انظر إلى هذا الجزء.
Where is An Yu?
أين أن يو؟
-An Yu... -I'm here.
-آن يو ... -أنا هنا.
Okay, I'll get to it.
حسنًا ، سأصل إليه.
I got the reports from the Risk Management Team.
حصلت على التقارير من فريق إدارة المخاطر.
The fire-fighting drones project
مشروع طائرات الإطفاء بدون طيار
has signed a pre-sale contract with the government.
وقع عقد ما قبل البيع مع الحكومة.
So its valuation
لذلك تقييمها
needs some adjustment.
يحتاج إلى بعض التعديل.
Noted.
وأشار.
The equity relationship between Pony Online
علاقة الإنصاف بين Pony Online
and its mother company, Stallion Education, needs more clarification.
وتحتاج شركتها الأم Stallion Education إلى مزيد من التوضيح.
Okay.
تمام.
Next, the targeted experiments
بعد ذلك ، التجارب المستهدفة
and clinical trials
والتجارب السريرية
by the peptide bio-pharmaceuticals need to be verified.
بواسطة المستحضرات الصيدلانية الحيوية الببتيد تحتاج إلى التحقق منها.
Also, they made available
أيضا ، جعلوا متاحين
16.7 points of their shares.
16.7 نقطة من حصصهم.
This needs to be confirmed
هذا يحتاج إلى تأكيد
with the intention of the team of scientists.
بقصد فريق العلماء.
Mr. Wang's company
شركة السيد وانغ
also sent us the latest report.
أرسل لنا أيضًا أحدث تقرير.
I will follow up with it.
سوف أتابع معها.
Alright, carry on.
حسنًا ، استمر.
Ding said you went out.
قال دينغ أنك خرجت.
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
I went to sign a contract with He Shuo.
ذهبت لتوقيع عقد مع He Shuo.
Why did you sign a contract with him?
لماذا وقعت عقدا معه؟
Lin Zhanhong is not an easy opponent.
لين Zhanhong ليس خصما سهلا.
Have you thought that maybe this is all a ruse?
هل فكرت أنه ربما يكون هذا كله خدعة؟
I'd know if it was a ruse.
كنت أعرف ما إذا كانت خدعة.
He Shuo is about to leave Yuqing.
هو Shuo على وشك مغادرة Yuqing.
I'd have missed the chance
كنت سأضيع الفرصة
if I didn't sign with him now.
إذا لم أوقع معه الآن.
Did you think I'd be stumped
هل تعتقد أنني سأكون في حيرة من أمري
because An Yu wouldn't sell me her shares?
لأن An Yu لن تبيع لي أسهمها؟
I got in touch with Zhuoyue's other shareholders.
لقد تواصلت مع المساهمين الآخرين في Zhuoyue.
If they agree to sell their shares to me,
إذا وافقوا على بيع أسهمهم لي ،
I can still achieve my goal.
لا يزال بإمكاني تحقيق هدفي.
Hello, Mr. Yuan.
مرحبا سيد يوان.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll be right there.
سأكون هناك.
You went to Yuan Wei?
هل ذهبت إلى يوان وي؟
You're taking an usury?
أنت تأخذ الربا؟
Tell me, are you?
اخبرني هل انت
Everyone already knows
الجميع يعرف بالفعل
that I'm using Yimi as leverage.
أنني أستخدم Yimi كرافعة مالية.
If I don't do this,
إذا لم أفعل هذا ،
I won't have the money to acquire Zhuoyue's shares.
لن أمتلك المال لشراء أسهم Zhuoyue.
So I have to do this.
لذلك علي أن أفعل هذا.
Zhou Yuan!
تشو يوان!
Get out of the car.
أخرج من السيارة.
Come out!
يظهر!
If you must be so reckless,
إذا كان يجب أن تكون متهورًا جدًا ،
our family will be wrecked.
ستدمر عائلتنا.
Yiyi is waiting for you at home.
Yiyi في انتظارك في المنزل.
Come out right now!
تعال الآن!
Zhou Yuan!
تشو يوان!
We managed to get through
تمكنا من العبور
all the things life threw at us before, no?
كل الأشياء التي ألقتها علينا الحياة من قبل ، أليس كذلك؟
Get out of the car.
أخرج من السيارة.
Come out!
يظهر!
We can talk this through...
يمكننا التحدث عن هذا من خلال ...
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
♪The brush depicting you♪
الفرشاة التي تصور لك ♪
♪Both blurry and clear♪
♪ كلاهما ضبابي وواضح ♪
♪The wind blows your dress up♪
♪ الرياح تهب فستانك ♪
♪You're like a poem♪
♪ أنت مثل القصيدة ♪
♪That captivates me♪
هذا يأسرني ♪
♪I listen to the wind and you quietly♪
♪ أستمع إلى الريح وأنت بهدوء ♪
♪The eraser that has removed our innocence♪
الممحاة التي أزالت براءتنا
♪I ask myself♪
♪ أسأل نفسي ♪
♪You're the reason I persevere♪
♪ أنت سبب مثابري ♪
♪You broke through the darkness♪
اخترقت الظلام ♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪ ونمت أجنحة جديدة
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪ يقودني إلى ضربة بضربة لخلق دراما ♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
لا يمكن استخلاصه ♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
أحدق فيك ، كلهم ​​مهووسون ، ولا يمكنني التوقف
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪ فتحت الدرج بغير قصد
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
التي احتفظت فيها بالرسومات التي رسمتها معك ♪
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪ لم نلتقي منذ بعض الوقت ♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪ ولا أعرف أين أنت الآن ♪
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪ صداقتنا المفقودة منذ زمن طويل ♪
♪Our future together♪
مستقبلنا معًا
♪You broke through the darkness♪
اخترقت الظلام ♪
♪And grew new wings♪
♪ ونمت أجنحة جديدة
♪Leading me stroke by stroke to create a drama♪
♪ يقودني إلى ضربة بضربة لخلق دراما ♪
♪That cannot be drawn♪
لا يمكن استخلاصه ♪
♪Staring at you, all obsessed, and I can't stop♪
أحدق فيك ، كلهم ​​مهووسون ، ولا يمكنني التوقف
♪I opened the drawer unintentionally♪
♪ فتحت الدرج بغير قصد
♪In which I kept the drawings I painted with you♪
التي احتفظت فيها بالرسومات التي رسمتها معك ♪
♪We haven't met for some time♪
♪ لم نلتقي منذ بعض الوقت ♪
♪And I don't know where you are now♪
♪ ولا أعرف أين أنت الآن ♪
♪Our long-lost friendship♪
♪ صداقتنا المفقودة منذ زمن طويل ♪
♪Our future together♪
مستقبلنا معًا
♪Waiting for you, in the future♪
في انتظارك في المستقبل ♪